<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WeConnect</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">WELCOME</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Free feel to start your first survey</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Navigation Drawer Menu-->
    <string name="menu_home">Home Page</string>
    <string name="menu_about_weconnect">About WeConnect</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="menu_admin_login">Admin Log in</string>
    <string name="menu_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>

    <!--  Content Description  -->
    <string name="main_admin_button">Enter Admin Page</string>
    <string name="main_volunteer_button">Enter Volunteer Page</string>
    <string name="logo">WeConnect Logo</string>
    <string name="survey_back_arrow">Click and go back to last page</string>
    <string name="cartoon">cartoon</string>
    <string name="volunteer_vic_logo">Volunteer Victoria Logo</string>
    <string name="volunteer_west_logo">Volunteer West Logo</string>


    <!--  Main Page  -->
    <string name="main_admin_text">Admin</string>
    <string name="main_volunteer_text">Volunteer</string>
    <string name="first_half_name">WeCo</string>
    <string name="second_half_name">nnect</string>

    <!--  Volunteer Home Page  -->
    <string name="take_survey_button">Take the survey</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>

    <!--  Take Survey Page Button  -->
    <string name="first_survey">First Survey</string>
    <string name="second_survey">Second Survey</string>
    <string name="survey_detail_btn">NEXT</string>
    <string name="survey_question_btn">PREVIOUS</string>
    <string name="police_agree">Agree and Continue</string>
    <string name="police_disagree">Disagree </string>

    <string name="sec_email_hint1">Your Email Address</string>
    <string name="sec_email_hint2">Note: To collect information more accurately, please ensure that
        the email address you provide matches the one from the first survey. \n
        Thank you for your cooperation.</string>
        
    <!-- Take Survey Title   -->
    <string name="personal_details">Personal Details</string>
    <string name="organisation_details">Organisation Details</string>
    <string name="survey_privacy_police">Your Personal Information And Data Privacy</string>

    <!--  Text Box Label  -->
    <string name="first_name">First Name*</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name*</string>
    <string name="email">Email*</string>
    <string name="postcode">Postcode*</string>
    <string name="choose_organisation">Choose your organisation*</string>
    <string name="cannont_find_organisation">Cannot find your organisation? Enter Here</string>
    <string name="manager_email">Manager Email</string>

    <!--  Hint Text  -->
    <string name="enter_first_name">Enter your first name here</string>
    <string name="enter_last_name">Enter your last name here</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Enter your email here</string>
    <string name="enter_postcode">Enter your postcode here </string>
    <string name="enter_organisation">Enter organisation name</string>
    <string name="enter_manager_email">Enter your manager email here</string>
    <string name="enter_answer">Enter your answer here</string>
    <string name="enter_search_country">Please enter your country</string>

    <!-- Organisation list   -->
    <string-array name="organisation_list">
        <item>VCOSS</item>
        <item>Volunteer Victoria</item>
        <item>Unimelb</item>
        <item>Volunteer West</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- privacy policy content   -->
    <string name="privacy_policy_text1">
        We collect your Personal Information for the primary
        purpose of providing our services to you.
    </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text2">
        Your Personal Information is stored in a manner that
        reasonably protects it from misuse and loss and from unauthorized access,
        modification or disclosure.
    </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text3">
        Further information, including the WeConnect Privacy Policy is available below.
    </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content">
        \n
         Volunteering Victoria Incorporated (we, our, us) recognises the importance of protecting the
    privacy and the rights of individuals in relation to their personal information. This document
    is our privacy policy and it tells you how we collect, use, hold and disclose your personal
    information.\n
        \n
    We respect your rights to privacy under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (Act) and, where we are
    required to do so, we comply with all of the Act’s requirements in respect of the collection,
    management and disclosure of your personal information.\n
        \n
        What is your personal information?\n
        \n
    When used in this Privacy Policy, the term ‘personal information’ has the meaning given to it
    in the Act. In general terms, it is any information that can be used to personally identify you.
    This may include your name, address, telephone number, email address and profession or
    occupation. If the information we collect personally identifies you, or you are reasonably
    identifiable from it, the information will be considered personal information.\n
        \n
What personal information do we collect and hold?\n
        \n
We may collect the following types of personal information:\n
 name;\n
 mailing or street address;\n
 email address;\n
 telephone number;\n
 name of organisation you work or volunteer for;\n
 profession, occupation or job title;\n
 details of the products and services you have obtained from us or which you
have enquired about, together with any additional information necessary to
deliver those products and services and to respond to your enquiries;\n
 any additional information relating to you that you provide to us directly, or
indirectly through our website or online presence, through our representatives
or otherwise; and\n
 information you provide to us through our office, surveys or visits by our
representatives from time to time.\n
        \n
We may also collect some information that is not personal information because it does not
identify you or anyone else. For example, we may collect anonymous answers to surveys or
aggregated information about how users use our website.\n
        \n
        For what purposes do we collect, hold, use and disclose your personal
information?\n
        \n
We collect personal information about you so that we can perform our activities and
functions and to provide best possible quality of service. In general terms, our relevant
activities and functions are:\n
• providing training and other events;\n
• providing membership services;\n
• advertising volunteer and paid positions online;\n
• answering volunteering queries; and\n
• providing information on our website and online presence.\n
        \n
We collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information for the following purposes:\n
• to provide products and services to you and to send communications requested
by you;\n
• to answer enquiries and provide information;\n
• to assess the performance of the website and to improve the operation of the
website;\n
• to conduct business processing functions, including providing personal
information to information to our contractors or service providers;\n
• for the administrative, planning, product or service development, quality control
and research purposes of Volunteering Victoria and our contractors or service
providers;\n
• to provide your updated personal information to our contractors or service
providers;\n
• to update our records and keep your contact details up to date;\n
• for the marketing (including direct marketing) purposes of Volunteering Victoria;
• to process and respond to any complaint made by you; and\n
• to comply with any law, rule, regulation, lawful and binding determination,
decision or direction of a regulator, or in co-operation with any governmental
authority of any country.\n
        \n
We will not use or disclose your personal information for any secondary purpose, unless the
following applies:\n
• that secondary purpose is related to the primary purpose for which the personal
information was collected;\n
• you would reasonably expect the use or disclosure;\n
• we have an obligation to use or disclose the information or there is another
permitted purpose; or\n
• you consent to the use or disclosure.\n
Your personal information will not be shared, sold, rented or disclosed other than as
described in this Privacy Policy.\n
        \n
        Security of personal information\n
        \n
        We take reasonable steps to ensure your personal information is held in a secure format and
protected from loss and misuse, as well as unauthorised access, modification, disclosure,
alteration, or destruction. We may hold your information in either electronic or hard copy
form. Personal information is destroyed or de-identified as soon as practicable when no
longer needed for the purpose it was collected. \n
We may hold the information we collect on systems managed and maintained by us and/or
our third-party cloud storage service provider who may create a backup of our data and
store that backup overseas. Any such backups of the data may be held in the United States
of America, Canada, Singapore, the UK or within the European Economic Area. Otherwise, we
do not, generally, disclose personal information to recipients outside of Australia.\n
As our website is linked to the internet, and the internet is inherently insecure, we cannot
provide any assurance regarding the security of transmission of information you
communicate to us online. We also cannot guarantee that the information you supply will
not be intercepted while being transmitted over the internet. Accordingly, any personal
information or other information which you transmit to us online is transmitted at your own
risk.\n
        \n
        An annual report shall be submitted to the Board to report on security of personal
information. The structure and content shall be agreed between the CEO and Board.\n
        \n
        Employee records\n
        \n
        We rely on the employee records exemption set out in the Act meaning that we do not need
to handle requests in respect of employee records in the same way as other types of
requests under this Privacy Policy.\n
        Links\n
        \n
        Our website may contain links to other websites operated by third parties. We make no
representations or warranties in relation to the privacy practices of any third-party website
and we are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of any third-party website.
Third party websites are responsible for informing you about their own privacy practices.\n
        \n
        How do we collect your personal information?\n
        \n
        We collect your personal information directly from you unless it is unreasonable or
impracticable to do so. When collecting personal information from you, we may collect in
ways including:\n
• through your access and use of our website or online presence (for example,
Twitter);\n
• during conversations between you and our representatives; or\n
• when you complete a membership application; register to attend training and
other events; subscribe to newsletters and other communications; advertise
volunteer or paid roles through our online databases; or complete a survey.\n
        \n
        1. Online forms\n
When you complete an online form which requests and collects personal information
directly from you. \n
        \n
2. Cookies\n
In some cases, we may also collect your personal information through the use of cookies.
When you access our website, we may send a “cookie” (which is a small summary file
containing a unique ID number) to your computer. This enables us to measure traffic
patterns, to determine which areas of our website have been visited and to measure
transaction patterns in the aggregate. We use this to research our users’ habits so that
we can improve our online products and services. Our cookies do not collect personal
information. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can set your browser so that your
computer does not accept them.\n
We may log IP addresses (that is, the electronic addresses of computers connected to the
internet) to analyse trends, administer the website, track users’ movements, and gather
broad demographic information.\n
        \n
3. Direct marketing materials\n
We may send you direct marketing communications and information about our products
and services that we consider may be of interest to you. These communications may be
sent in various forms, including mail, SMS, and email, in accordance with applicable
marketing laws, such as the Spam Act 2003 (Cth). If you indicate a preference for a
method of communication, we will endeavour to use that method whenever practical to
do so. In addition, at any time you may opt-out of receiving marketing communications
from us by contacting us (see the details below) or by using opt-out facilities provided in
the marketing communications and we will then ensure that your name is removed from
our mailing list. We do not provide your personal information to other organisations for
the purposes of direct marketing. \n
        \n
What happens if we can’t collect your personal information?\n
        \n
If you do not provide us with the personal information described above, some or all of the
following may happen:\n
• we may not be able to provide the requested products or services to you, either
to the same standard or at all;\n
• we may not be able to provide you with information about products and services
that you may want; or\n
• we may be unable to tailor the content of our websites to your preferences and
your experience of our websites may not be as enjoyable or useful.\n
To whom may we disclose your information?\n
        \n
We may disclose your personal information to:\n
• our employees, volunteers, contractors or service providers for the purposes of
operation of our website or our business, fulfilling requests by you, and to
otherwise provide products and services to you; and\n
• any organisation for any authorised purpose with your express consent.\n
Our contractors or service providers may include, without limitation: our website developer,
the providers of any systems such as Membes, Viktor Online (Volunteering Western Australia
and Eduka), web hosting providers, IT systems administrators, mailing houses, couriers,
payment processors, data entry service providers, electronic network administrators, debt
collectors, and professional advisors such as our accountant, business advisors and solicitors.\n
        \n
Disclosure of Personal Information\n
        \n
Personal information may be disclosed in a number of circumstances including the following:\n
• to third parties where you consent to the use or disclosure; and\n
• where required or authorised by law.\n
        \n
How can you access and correct your personal information?\n
        \n
You may request access to any personal information we hold about you at any time by
contacting us (see the details below). \n
Where we hold information that you are entitled to access, we will try to provide you with
suitable means of accessing it (for example, by mailing or emailing it to you). We will not
charge for providing your personal information to you and will not charge for making any
corrections to your personal information. \n
There may be instances where we cannot grant you access to the personal information we
hold. For example, we may need to refuse access if granting access would interfere with the
privacy of others or if it would result in a breach of confidentiality. If that happens, we will
give you written reasons for any refusal. \n
If you believe that personal information we hold about you is incorrect, incomplete or
inaccurate, then you may request us to amend it. We will consider if the information requires
amendment. If we do not agree that there are grounds for amendment then we will add a
note to the personal information stating that you disagree with it. \n
        \n
What is the process for complaining about a breach of privacy?\n
        \n
If you believe that your privacy has been breached, please contact us using the contact
information below and provide details of the incident so that we can investigate it.
Contacting us\n
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, any concerns or a complaint regarding
the treatment of your privacy or a possible breach of your privacy, please contact us using
the details set out below.\n
We will treat your requests or complaints confidentially. Our representative will contact you
within a reasonable time after receipt of your complaint to discuss your concerns and outline
options regarding how they may be resolved. We will aim to ensure that your complaint is
resolved in timely and appropriate manner.\n
        \n
Please contact us at:\n
Volunteering Victoria\n
Post: Our Community House, \n
552 Victoria Street\n
North Melbourne VIC 3051\n
Tel: 03 9052-4524\n
Email: info@volunteeringvictoria.org.au\n
    </string>

    <!--  About WeConnect  -->
    <string name="intro_text1">
        WeConnect is a Collective impact tool  to collect data about a volunteer’s
        experience, skills and change within three domains, which are Volunteer Wellbeing,
        Volunteer Confidence and Volunteer to Job potential.
    </string>
    <string name="intro_vv_text1">
        Volunteering Victoria
    </string>
    <string name="intro_vv_text2">
        “Building an inclusive, thriving volunteering culture”
    </string>
    <string name="intro_vw_text1">
        Volunteer West
    </string>
    <string name="intro_vw_text2">
        “Our key focus is on strengthening the volunteering sector
        and supporting organisational development.”
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_nav_testing">NavTesting</string>

    <!-- Contact Us   -->
    <string name="contact_us_image">contact us image</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="contact_us_content">For further information, please contact WeConnect via
        email weconnect@volunteeringvictoria.org.au.</string>

    <!--  Error hint  -->
    <string name="empty_hint">The text box cannot be empty</string>

    <!-- Survey questions   -->
    <string name="type_short_answer_question_text_sample">What was your role?</string>
    <string name="type_enter_number_question_text_sample">How many new connections have you
        made while volunteering? </string>
    <string name="type_rating_1_5_question_text_sample">Has volunteering helped you to practice the
         Connect of wellbeing?
</string>
    <string name="type_rating_1_10_question_text_sample">Would you recommend Volunteer West to your
        friends or anyone who want to volunteer?</string>
    <string name="type_yes_or_no_question_text_sample">Are you volunteering due to Centrelink
        requirement?</string>
    <string name="type_search_dropdown_question_text_sample">Country of Birth:</string>
    <string name="type_multiple_choices_question_text_sample">Single choice question text sample?</string>

    <string name="option1">Option 1</string>
    <string name="option2">Option 2</string>
    <string name="option3">Option 3</string>
    <string name="option4">Option 4</string>

    <string name="rating1">1</string>
    <string name="rating2">2</string>
    <string name="rating3">3</string>
    <string name="rating4">4</string>
    <string name="rating5">5</string>
    <string name="rating6">6</string>
    <string name="rating7">7</string>
    <string name="rating8">8</string>
    <string name="rating9">9</string>
    <string name="rating10">10</string>
    <string name="question_story">Story</string>
    <string name="question_wellbeing">Wellbeing</string>
    <string name="question_employability">Employability</string>
    <string name="question_volunteer_confidence">Volunteer confidence</string>
    <string name="question_demographic_question">Demographic question</string>
    <string name="question_service">Service</string>

    <string name="degree_agree">strongly agree</string>
    <string name="degree_disagree">strongly disagree</string>
    <string name="weak_degree">weak</string>
    <string name="strong_degree">strong</string>

    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>

    <!--  Congrats Page  -->
    <string name="congrats">CONGRATS!</string>
    <string name="thanks_for_submit">thank you for submitting</string>
    <string name="return_home_page">back home page</string>


</resources>